http://www.grahamfrp.com/en/privacy-policy/

Brands
Glasliner (Exceliner)
Glasliner (Exceliner)
Wall Panels
Ceiling Tiles
Foundation Liners
Door Skin
Poliacryl (Polylit)
Poliacryl (Polylit)
Poliacryl Plus (Polylit Plus)
Tred-Safe Deck
Fire-Snuf CR (FS25A)
Request Samples
F.A.Q.
Contact Us
Privacy PolicyHome Privacy Policy
Glasteel is sensitive to the privacy issues, which may concern our website visitors. We believe it is important that you know how we treat your personal information as we receive it through this Website or the Internet (the “Website” or “Website Service”). This Privacy Policy explains what type of information we collect from Website users, what we do with the information, and how users can access the information provided through this Website.When information is needed, we will try to let you know how that information will be used at the time of collection. Usually, the personal information we collect is used only by Glasteel to respond to your inquiry.If you register within our Website, we may use this information to provide you with customized content regarding Glasteel offerings in support of your business needs. However, you are not required to provide personal information as a condition of using our Website, except as may be necessary to provide you a product or service at your request.We will retain control of the use of any personal data you disclose to Glasteel through the Website. Some of this data may be stored or processed at computers located in other jurisdictions, whose data protection laws may differ from the jurisdiction in which you live. In such cases, we will ensure that appropriate protections are in place to require the data processor in that country to maintain protections on the data that are equivalent to those that apply in the country in which you live.The Website may contain links to other sites such as Glasteel's distributors and sales affiliates. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.If you don't want to be contacted in the future by the company whose website you entered, or if you would like us to correct or update your personal information in our records, please contact us.Terms of UseGeneralThis Website Service is provided by Glasteel and its affiliated business units and is to be used for information purposes only. The following agreement governs your use of the Website Service, including any interactive areas. Additional terms and conditions of use applicable to specific areas of the Website Service may also be posted in such areas and, together with this agreement (the "Agreement"), govern your use of those areas.Glasteel reserves the right, in its discretion, to change or modify all or any part of this Agreement at any time, effective immediately upon notice published on the Website Service. Your continued use of the Website Service constitutes your binding acceptance of these terms and conditions, including any changes or modifications made by Glasteel as permitted above. If at any time the terms and conditions of this Agreement are no longer acceptable to you, you should immediately cease all use of the Website Service.Use of Content – Propietary InformationYou acknowledge that the Website Service contains information, software, photographs, graphics, links and other material (collectively, the "Content") that are protected by copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights of Glasteel or third parties. All Content on the Website Service is copyrighted as a collective work of Glasteel pursuant to applicable copyright law. You agree to comply with any additional copyright notices, information, or restrictions contained in any Content available on or accessed through the Website Service. Users of the Website Service may use the Content only for their personal, noncommercial use.You may not modify, publish, transmit, transfer or sell, reproduce, create derivative works from, distribute, perform, display, or in any way exploit any of the Content, in whole or in part, except as expressly permitted in this Agreement. If applicable, you may post on the Website Service only Content owned by you, or for which you have received express permission from the owner, or Content in the public domain.Except as expressly permitted by the copyright laws, no copying, storage, redistribution or publication of any Content is permitted without the express permission of Glasteel or the owners of such Content or their authorized persons, if other than Glasteel.You agree that any information or materials that you or individuals acting on your behalf provide to Glasteel will not be considered confidential or proprietary. By providing any such information or materials to Glasteel, you grant to Glasteel an unrestricted, irrevocable, worldwide, royalty-free license to use, reproduce, display, publicly perform, transmit and distribute such information and materials, and you further agree that Glasteel is free to use any ideas, concepts or know-how that you or individuals acting on your behalf provide to Glasteel.Rules of ConductYou shall not post on the Website Service any Content which (a) is defamatory, obscene, pornographic, abusive, harassing or threatening, (b) contains viruses or other contaminating or destructive features, (c) violates the rights of others, such as Content which infringes any copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret or violates any right of privacy or publicity, or (d) otherwise violates any applicable law.Managing ContentGlasteel does not and cannot review the Content posted by users on the Website Service and is not responsible for such Content. However, Glasteel reserves the right to delete, move or edit any Content that it may determine, in its sole discretion, violates this Agreement or is otherwise unacceptable. You shall remain solely responsible for all Content posted by you. Glasteel shall have the right, but not the obligation, to correct any errors or omissions in any Content, as it may determine in its sole discretion.Link SitesThe Website Service may contain links to sites on the Internet which are owned and operated by third parties (the "Link Sites"). You acknowledge that Glasteel is not responsible for the availability of, or the content located on or through, any Link Site. You should contact the site administrator or Webmaster for those Link Sites if you have any concerns regarding such links or the content located on such Link Sites.Use of CookiesThis site service may use “cookies” in order to improve the efficiency of its individual use by the site service users. The “cookies” are small database files, formed typically by a chain of numbers and letters, which assign a unique identification to each user. The users may adjust their web browser so they can be informed whenever they receive a “cookie” or to prevent sending one; if the users adjust their web browser, the functionality of the site service may be affected or limited.This privacy policy will apply to each and every section and web page of the website known as: www.glasteel.com Our users privacy is very important to us, therefore, we inform how we use their information, which is not collected, used, sold or shared without prior consent of the users.We use “cookies” with the sole purpose of providing the users a more personalized treatment, under the premise that the users are on the website by their own free will. Al the collected and saved data will be the one that the users provided by their own free will.Through the “cookies” we can reach the users with a more personalized publicity while they surf web pages that form part of Google´s Display Network or social networks such as Facebook or Twitter.The way we use the “cookies” is through Google Adwords platform, because the “cookies” are never stored in our site service.All users have the possibility of configuring and personalizing their web browser as to the treatment of the “cookies”, such as to prohibit their installation on their computers, know what “cookies” they have already installed in their web browser, how long can they last and their administration. Users can consult the instructions and manuals of their web browser to amplify this information.If the users wish not to have any publicity bases on their interests on their web browser, they can click on the disable button https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/?hl=es of the administrator of advertising preferences. For any question regarding the use of the information and personal data or the “cookies” of this website you can send an email to privacy.policy@glasteel.comIndemnityYou agree to indemnify, defend and hold Glasteel and its affiliated business units, and their respective officers, directors, owners, agents, information providers and licensors (collectively, the "Glasteel Parties") harmless from and against any and all claims, liability, losses, costs and expenses (including attorneys' fees) incurred by any Glasteel Party in connection with any use or alleged use of the Website Service under your password by any person, whether or not authorized by you. Glasteel reserves the right, at its own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you, and in such case, you agree to cooperate with Glasteel's defense of such claim.Modification or Termination of Website ServiceGlasteel reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to restrict, suspend or terminate your access to all or any part of the Website Service, at any time for any reason without prior notice or liability. Glasteel may change, modify, suspend or discontinue all or any aspect of the Website Service at any time, including the availability of any feature, database, or Content, without prior notice or liability.Warranties - Limitation of LiabilityNEITHER GLASTEEL NOR ANY PROVIDER OF THIRD PARTY CONTENT OR THEIR RESPECTIVE AGENTS WARRANTS THAT THE SERVICE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE; NOR DOES GLASTEEL, ANY THIRD PARTY CONTENT PROVIDER, OR THEIR RESPECTIVE AGENTS MAKE ANY WARRANTY AS TO THE RESULTS TO BE OBTAINED FROM USE OF THE SERVICE OR THE CONTENT. THE WEBSITE SERVICE AND THE CONTENT ARE DISTRIBUTED ON AN "AS IS, AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. NONE OF GLASTEEL, THIRD PARTY CONTENT PROVIDERS AND THEIR RESPECTIVE AGENTS MAKE ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES OF TITLE OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, WITH RESPECT TO THE WEBSITE SERVICE, OR ANY CONTENT OR ANY PRODUCTS OR SERVICES SOLD THROUGH THE WEBSITE SERVICE. NEITHER Glasteel NOR ANY THIRD PARTY CONTENT PROVIDER WARRANTS THAT ANY FILES AVAILABLE FOR DOWNLOADING THROUGH THE WEBSITE SERVICE WILL BE FREE OF VIRUSES OR SIMILAR CONTAMINATION OR DESTRUCTIVE FEATURES. GLASTEEL ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER OR COMPUTER SYSTEM AS A RESULT OF USES OF THE WEBSITE SERVICE OR THE CONTENT.NEITHER GLASTEEL, ANY THIRD PARTY CONTENT PROVIDER NOR THEIR RESPECTIVE AGENTS SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE WEBSITE SERVICE, EVEN IF Glasteel HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS OR EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN SUCH STATES, THE LIABILITY OF GLASTEEL, THIRD PARTY CONTENT PROVIDERS AND THEIR RESPECTIVE AGENTS SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE GREATEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.Entire AgreementThis Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between Glasteel and you with respect to your use of the Website Service. Any claim or cause of action you may have with respect to your use of the Website Service must be commenced within one (1) year after the claim or cause of action arises. If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of the Agreement or portion thereof, to be unenforceable, that provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent permissible so as to effect the intent of the Agreement, and the remainder of this Agreement shall continue in full force and effect.
Our markets
Commercial+
Commercial
Interior Wall & Ceiling CladdingTop Hygienic Wall & Ceiling CladdingRefrigeration Interior Wall & Ceiling CladdingFoundation LinerRoof Light & SidelightCanopies & Light Roofing
Institutional+
Institutional
Interior Wall & Ceiling CladdingTop Hygienic Interior Wall & Ceiling CladdingRoof Lights & GlazingCanopies & Light Roofing
Architectural+
Architectural
Roofing & SkylightsCurtain Walls & PartitionsCovered Walkways
Commercial Greenhouse+
Commercial Greenhouse
Agricultural+
Agricultural
Livestock Roofing & CladdingAgricultural Warehouses
Industrial+
Industrial
Industrial Roof Lights & SidelightsInterior Wall & Ceiling CladdingIndustrial Roofing & SidingDecking
High Spec Industrial+
High Spec Industrial
Roof Light & SidelightRoofing & Siding PanelsDeck ProductsLouvers & VentilatorsAccessories, Flashing & Gutters
Residential+
Residential
Translucent Light RoofsOpaque Light RoofsInterior Wall CladdingFoundation LinerDecoration
Transportation+
Transportation
Truck & TrailersRecreational VehiclesBuses & Ambulances
Health Care+
Health Care
Hygienic Interior Wall & Ceiling CladdingAntimicrobial Interior Wall & Ceiling Cladding
Transformation+
Transformation
SignalizationDecorationRefrigeration
Follow us
Graham FRP
Sitemap
Privacy Policy
Stabilit is a company of group
® All rights reserved Verzatec.
Company
About Us Green Initiative Certifications & Associations
Products
FRP Liner Panel
Glasliner FRP Wall Panels Glasliner Ceiling Tiles Glasliner Foundation Liners Glasliner Door Skins
Roofing & Siding Panels
Daylighting Panels Opaque Roofing & Siding Panels Canopies & Lightweight Roofing Greenhouses
Transportation
Recreational Vehicles Truck & Trailers Autobuses & Ambulances Door Skins
Others
Deck Products Louvers & Ventilators Accessories
Brands
Glasliner (Exceliner)
Glasliner (Exceliner)
Poliacryl (Polylit)
Poliacryl (Polylit) Poliacryl Plus (Polylit Plus)
Acrylit
Acrylit Acrylit High Impact Acrylit High Performance
Macrolux
Macrolux Multiwall Macrolux Rooflite Macrolux Systems
Vinylit Steeliner
Steeliner
Versalit
Versalit Versalit Premium
Opalit
Opalit
Tred-Safe
Tred-Safe Translucent Tred-Safe Opaque Tred-Safe Deck
Fire-Snuf CR (FS25A)
Fire-Snuf CR Translucent Fire-Snuf CR Opaque RFM
Applications
Commercial
Interior Wall & Ceiling Cladding Top Hygienic Wall & Ceiling Cladding Refrigeration Interior Wall & Ceiling Cladding Foundation Liner Roof Light & Sidelight Canopies & Light Roofing
Institutional
Interior Wall & Ceiling Cladding Top Hygienic Interior Wall & Ceiling Cladding Roof Lights & Glazing Canopies & Light Roofing
Architectural
Roofing & Skylights Curtain Walls & Partitions Covered Walkways
Commercial Greenhouse Agricultural
Livestock Roofing & Cladding Agricultural Warehouses
Industrial
Industrial Roof Lights & Sidelights Interior Wall & Ceiling Cladding Industrial Roofing & Siding Decking
High Spec Industrial
Roof Light & Sidelight Roofing & Siding Panels Deck Products Louvers & Ventilators Accessories, Flashing & Gutters
Residential
Translucent Light Roofs Opaque Light Roofs Interior Wall Cladding Foundation Liner Decoration
Transportation
Truck & Trailers Recreational Vehicles Buses & Ambulances
Health Care
Hygienic Interior Wall & Ceiling Cladding Antimicrobial Interior Wall & Ceiling Cladding
Transformation
Signalization Decoration Refrigeration
Support
Downloads Request Samples F.A.Q.
Search for:
